Baby in my heart,
Every passionate thought is about you,
Like a fire burning
Shape of your body
Won’t let me keep my eyes off (I'm always checking you out)
I’m indulged
You linger close to my heart
As if I’ve known you forever (you are a familiar feeling)
You look like a goddess
My mind is exhilarating
you are the dearest
You linger close to my heart
As if I’ve known you forever (you are a familiar feeling)
You look like a goddess
My mind is exhilarating
you are the dearest
Baby in my heart
Let’s not make this complicated
You found my heart that I kept hidden
My love is only valid for you
Let’s not hold our horses anymore
You’re the talkative one of the whole village
My heart has become your victim
When our eyes meet
I can’t control myself
Girl, oh Girl..
My heart is on fire
Come a little closer
Your charms make me go crazy
You were inviting
I’m a bee looking for honey
I’m the one you should be with (Forget everyone else around)
Baby in my heart
Every passionate thought is about you
Looking like a goddess
My mind is exhilarating,
you are the dearest
You linger close to my heart
As if I’ve known you forever (you are a familiar feeling)
Looking like a goddess
My mind is exhilarating,
you are the dearest
Baby in my heart
Every passionate thought is about you,
Like a fire burning
Shape of your body
Won’t let me keep my eyes off
I’m indulged
You linger close to my heart
As if I’ve known you forever
Looking like a goddess,
My mind is exhilarating,
you are the dearest
You linger close to my heart
As if I’ve known you forever
Looking like a goddess, My mind is exhilarating, you are the dearest !
Baby in my heart